Hello, I'm going to show you our website.
The title of the page is Mini Health Encyclopedia.
On the main page, we can find a content index
to navigate and jump to the section we're interested in.
For example, we can go to the index in the search section, where we can choose a letter to see the corresponding articles.
There’s also a tab with featured articles,
and a site map where we can check all the information on the page.
We also find two forms, one if you haven’t found what you were looking for, and another to contact us.
The page also includes an accessibility statement with all the guidelines it follows (as declared by the WCAG).
Additionally, there are two PDFs to show what a properly accessible PDF would look like, and another showing improper accessibility.
Let’s access the articles that start with the letter "E";
in this case, there is only one article, which is about pregnancy.
We can see in the breadcrumbs where we are on the website. In addition, most of the articles follow a similar structure,
where there’s an index that lets us jump to the section we're interested in, such as the description, causes, symptoms, or whatever we like.
Moreover, in this particular article, we have a table that is fully usable and accessible.
Also, this article includes an interactive map where we can select the part we’re interested in, and it will tell us more about it.
At the end of the article, so that we don’t have to scroll all the way back up, we can click a button to return to the main page.
In this mini-tutorial, as we’ve been navigating through the website, there’s still much more to explore.
So, I invite you to visit our website and discover everything else that’s waiting to be seen.